Hello to the insurance giants, if
you have seen it, now IC Bank,
IC Left Bank, you have a
policy of insurance of ₹1000 per month and ₹12000 per year. In
that policy, if you have seen it, you
have a lot of good benefits. If you have seen it,
you can go to our OP and get any of our treatments for free,
bed charges are all
inclusive, if you
have seen it, if you have seen it once, then if you get sick
for some reason, it
costs 5 lakhs to 6 lakhs rupees, then they make a
full claim and give it to you,
after that we do not get the same disease,
even if someone else comes to our house, we are
not going to get anything. Even if it comes like that, it
comes back and something else, our
disease, if it comes,
it is like an auto refill.  If
you pay ₹12,000 a year, it costs us only ₹1,000 a month,
but we can claim all the
hospital expenses, medical expenses, and bed charges.
ICI Bank now has a
lot of people
claiming like this. If you
want insurance,
contact me. My number is
9786439560. You can get our manager to do this and get
our policy. You can get your
policy yourself. You can come and get all
this and get it. They
give you all kinds of easy packs. If you don't have any of them,
you can ask for them. If
you see our clients, you have different types of
claims for each disease. For
some diseases, we don't have any disease, but
we have a new disease, and we have a new disease, and we have a
claim for 30 days, 31 days, and we have a claim for
some of our diseases.  If you see that a claim
comes like this for a year or two and
suddenly we have
a
situation like this,
we can do it like that, we can do it like that,
we can decide how to do it,
so if you don't
see this insurance month of ₹1000 and
put ₹12000 for a year, you will have to
pay for the hospital, our emergency even if we have
money in our hand or
not, we can use it, we
can use it, this is good information, if you
want this opportunity,
what do you want, call me, I will tell my manager to
contact you and talk to you.
Thank you,
greetings, Health Kerala
Magic, this is your
annual health cover for 20 lakhs, claim this, reset, claim
again in the same year, reset claim,
reset claim, reset claim,
reset unlimited  Reset bro ICC
Love Elimit Health Insurance with
Unlimited Reset Benefit,
have you ever heard of this type of
insurance?